sg-micro.com 2017-02-07

# SG Micro Corp

## Privacy Policy 

SG Micro Corp highly respects and rigorously protects personal information and privacy of each customer. The Privacy Policy is deemed to ensure the security of personal information and using this website indicates that you accept the terms of our privacy policy and the changes we made to the Terms from time to time.

(1)  Collection and Use of Personal Information

Visitors to the SG Micro Corp’s web site are not required to reveal any personal information in order to use many of the features of the site. However, in some instances such as registering an account or making a purchase, SG Micro Corp requests that users provide certain personal information in order to facilitate future communications, make a purchase of the products, or receive materials or other information from SG Micro Corp. SG Micro Corp will only use the information you provided for legitimate business purposes which may include sharing some information with our authorized distributors and assisting you in making a purchase of our products.

(2)  Protection of Personal Information

Personal information including user's name, mailing address, email address, etc. will be protected from being obtained by unauthorized third parties. SG Micro Corp will not share your information with any third party without authorization.

Please do not provide your account info, passwords and other information to others. If you find that your account has been used illegally, please notify us immediately.

You can log into your account to view and modify your personal information at any time. When you finished using your account at this website, please remember to log out and your personal information will not be seen by others.

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us. SG Micro Corp is committed to the full protection of user information, and will provide you with better experience and service.
